All right, so let's start off by creating a new source file under Maine.
And call it S&P Time Sink.
Gutsy.
And now create a new header file.
And it's S&P time sink.
And now let's go to see make lists.
And let's add here, the S&P time sync.
That see file.
All right, so now we can go to tasks coming.
And here let's go to the very bottom in here.
And let's add the information.
For the S&P Time Sync Task.
And now let's define S&P time sink.
And now a copy this part and its stack size.
And make it four thousand ninety six.
The next defined priority as for.
And the core idea.
As one.
OK, so we're good to go.
So now we can go to the time sink header.
And now here we're going to define a couple of function prototypes.
And first, let's define a prototype that starts the A.P. server.
Synchronization task.
And it's a void S&P time sink Teske start.
And it's void.
OK, now let's define another prototype, which returns local time.
If set and the return is the local time buffer.
OK, so the return is a point to.
And it's S&P time sink.
Get time.
And it's void.
All right, so that's it.
So now we can copy this.
And we can head over to the see file and to find them there.
And let's first just put them here, and I'll clean them up a bit.
All right, so we'll define those later.
Now let's just go up and include here ESP luggage.
And now include.
Free autos slash free auto, Sturridge.
And also include.
Free autos.
Slash task, dunwich.
And next include.
Lightweight IP apps, S.A. Pietrowicz.
And now for our application includes let's include tasks common.
And we also need to include.
FTP server.
We also need to include our.
S&P time sink.
Courage.
And lastly, let's include.
Include the wife at that age.
OK, now I'll just build to resolve these unresolved includes you.
Whoops, I tried to save.
Well, it's building, so that's OK, I'll just let it continue.
OK, so we're back, right, so here, let's do a static const care.
And call it S&P Time Sink.
And because I had prefer having the task start function at the bottom of the file.
I'll just move it there.
And then here we'll use X to create PIN to Core.
And the tax code is a reference to S&P time sink.
And the name is also S&P time sync.
When the stack depth S&P time sync task.
Stack size.
PV parameters are no.
And the priority is as interview time sink to ask priority.
And the test scandal is now in the core idea is the S&P time sync task.
Caller ID.
Now, let's create the S&P Time Sync function.
And let's do it here.
It'll be the soon to be time synchronization task.
And the parameter ARG is a point of variable parameter.
It's a static void.
And it's our time sync task.
And it's a void pointer.
PV Perram.
Now here, let's create an infinite loop and we can use a wild one.
And in here, we'll call the centipede time sink, obtain time function, and we'll define this shortly.
So it's the S&P time sink, obtain time.
And now we can add a delay here and in our implementation, we'll continue checking if the time is updated
based on this delay.
But of course, you can adjust this to your needs, or maybe you even want to kill the task once the
time is up to date, for example.
So here, let's use B tasks delay.
And let's do this every ten thousand milliseconds.
OK, and should the task implementation of a breakout of the above loop, we can call vortex delete.
So let's do that.
In personal to it.
OK, so next, let's define the uptick in time function.
And up here, let's say.
Gets the current time.
And if the current time is not up to date.
The S&P time sync.
And S&P.
Function is called.
And it's a static void up to in time, and it's void.
And first of all, say, time type now equals zero.
And next will create the time infrastructure in here, use struct Tim and call it time info and now
set it to zero.
Like so.
And now we'll call the time function and pass a reference to our time type variable.
Now.
The next use, the local time underscore our function to update the TM structure.
So let's call local time, underscore I.
And pass a reference to now.
And a reference to time info.
All right, so next, we'll check the time.
In case we need to initialize.
Slash re initialize.
So, right, if time info does you.
Is less than twenty sixteen minus 9500.
Then we should S&P time sink.
In it, S&P.
So we'll call this function if the time is not up to date, and we'll define it shortly.
So next, we'll set the local time zone.
And you set envy and specify to.
And now I'll into my time zone, and so you can just into yours as well.
And you could set the last parameter as one.
All right.
So you can check the file that I've attached in the resources and look for your time zone there and
then just enter it here.
OK, next call to set.
And that's to initialize the time zone conversion routine.
OK, so next, we need a global variable here for the S&P operating mode status.
And we need this variable because we only want to set the operating mode once.
So it's a static pool.
S&P Up mode set.
Instead, it's a false.
OK.
And next, let's define the initialize S&P function will come into you, initialize S&P service.
Using S&P Up mode poll mode.
OK, so I'll copy the function.
And here it's static void.
And it's void.
And first, let's S.P. lug.
And say initializing.
The centrepiece service.
Now, right, if not, S&P Up mode said.
So if it's not set, will set the operating mode.
Using S&P set operating mode and then pass S&P Up mode pull.
And then now we can set this variable to true.
And then next, we can call S&P set ServerName.
And the first parameter is zero.
And the second is pool that A.P. talk.
And now we can initialize the servers.
Using S&P in it.
And then we can let the FTP server know.
Service is initialized.
By calling a CTB server monitor.
Send a message and we'll create a new message for this and call it HTP message time service initialized.
All right, so that will be our new message for the FTP server, and we'll define it later.
For now, let's just go to the get time function.
And will return a buffer here, so it needs to be a static care and call it time buffer.
And one hundred bytes should be enough and set it to zero.
All right.
So I'll make a little room here.
Then let's use the time type now instead of two zero.
And we also need our struct. team time info.
And set that to zero.
And then call the time function with a reference to now.
The now called local time underscored our.
In reference now and then reference time for.
Then let's do a check and say if time info that TMU.
Is less than.
Twenty sixteen, minus nineteen hundred.
Then we'll ESP log.
Time is not set yet.
Then they'll say else.
And then now we can call CRF Time.
And this function is similar to aspirin death, which enables formatting the time and date string.
OK, so first we'll do this to the time buffer.
For the size of.
The time buffer.
And then now will format the day.
The month.
The year.
And the hour.
And the second.
OK, and we'll get the information from time info.
And then let's S.P. lug.
The current time info.
From the time buffer.
And then we can return the time buffer.
So now we can copy our new message.
And then let's go define it in the HTTP server header.
And let's just included as a message right here.
All right, so that's it for now.
Let's continue in the next lesson.